

# **CONTACT ME**

- Haryana, India
- rajatraghuvanshi1507@gmail.com
- +91 9034101507
- Rajat-Raghuvanshi-1507

# **EDUCATION**

#### **B.E CSBS**

**Chandigarh University** 

CGPA (current) - 8.4

2020 - 2024

### Senior Secondary (XII), Science

**Pratap Public School** 

Percentage - 92.6%

2019 - 2020

# **SKILLS**

Javascript

N NextJs

(S) NodeJs

Mongo DB

React Native

# **HOBBIES**



**Football** 







Music

# RAJAT RAGHUVANSHI

### Full Stack Web Developer

https://rajatraghuvanshi.netlify.app

# ABOUT ME

Creative web developer with experience in building, optimizing and maintaining the performance of user centric websites. Clear understanding of modern technologies and best design practices. An ambitious problem solver willing to join a team of like-minded people.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Associate Software Developer

Dec 2023 - Current



As a dedicated professional, I excel in constructing, enhancing, and streamlining web and mobile applications for esteemed organizations. I have honed my proficiency in the MERN stack and React Native to an expert level. Leading a dynamic team, I ensure the timely delivery of exceptional results.

Full Stack Web Developer

May 2023 - Oct 2023



Responsible for building maintaining and optimizing web applications for reputed companies. Polished my MERN stack skills to expert level and lead the team to deliver the results within the stipulated period of time. Good interpersonal & communicaiton skills to deal and meet with the client's requirements.

Backend Developer (Team Head)

Nov 2022 - May 2023



Lead the team of 12 members and maintained main server(AWS) of the company. Added numerous features like Payment Gateways, Notifications, International currency conversion. Played an important role in the development of new Startup website. Learnt important tools like Slack, Jira, Notion etc.

# FREELANCE PROJECTS

### Timmy's Mowing (NextJs)

September 2023 - October 2023

Link: https://timmysmowing.au

### Lazer Crazer (Pug & NodeJs)

January 2022 - March 2022

Link: https://lazercrazer.in

Mother's Kitchen (MERN Stack)

May 2023 - June 2023

Link: https://motherskitchen.co.in

### **Chat App (React + Firebase)**

June 2022 - July 2022

Link: https://chat-app-c8964.web.app

# **ACHIEVEMENTS**

- IBM certified Full Stack Software Developer Professional
- Won Ideathon 2023 organised by Standard Chartered Bank.
- Won 'Academic Excellence Award' for the 2022-23 session.